Don't you guys think it's a waste of
our money because of insurance?
Don't bash me guys, I just
really want to say
my honest opinion about this. So if
you think what I said is wrong, I'm open
to correction here in the comments. So how did
I say that insurance is losing money
because it works?
Ian by paying small amounts on a regular
basis, so you pay monthly or annually,
or whatever. It depends on your mode of
payment, then you will receive a
large amount of money or
your coverage, you will get it when
the clim condition in the contract comes, for
example, life insurance, so the claim
condition is that when the insured dies,
the
beneficiaries of health insurance will receive money. If
you have a serious illness,
you will receive money for treatment, but
think about it. What if you didn't get
sick because you tried to be
healthy, you exercised
every day, you ate healthy
food, you didn't have any vices, and you didn't
really get sick because of that? So does that
mean that you won't get anything because
you didn't get sick, you didn't
make any claims? Shouldn't there be more reward?
We are the people because of
being healthy because think about it so that
you can benefit from health
insurance let's say you became healthy
diving Why don't you be unhealthy
do those things just to get
sick just to benefit from
the insurance so it's like Of course
we don't want to do that second
maybe tell me here it's good Ed
get vul or what we call
variable unit link or the insurance that
has an investment because they will say
if you claim you get sick or
die there will be money if
you don't use it there is an investment in the
policy But if you read the
contract itself the money
you pay is divided there some goes to the
insurance some goes to the
investment So that means all the money
that goes to the insurance is the
company's income they just make it look like it's
worth it because in the investment part they will
show you a projection of 10%
per anum cheese if you are 40 years old
this much you will get when you are 50 when
you are 60 or 65 years old the
money will be bigger because you are
working on the computer overtime but think about it  You have
10% per anum, it's too big, there is
risk involved and the
growth of the investment depends on the performance of the
underlying asset where
your money is put, for example in the stock market in
large companies in the Philippines. So if
you think about it, what about people who are not
risk takers or people who don't want to
risk their hard earned money
in these types of investments?
Also, what if when they needed the
money, the investment fell, the
asset,
for example, our stock market before the
pandemic was high? So what if
the person invested there, there was a
pandemic, it fell because of the pandemic, that's when
they needed the money. So that means they lost money.
Because they bought it expensively, they sold it
cheaply. In which
investment should be, you bought it cheaply,
you sell it expensively so you can make a profit. So that's why
I thought, is there
insurance that you know that if you don't
use it, you don't get sick, you
become healthy, you will be given money again
because you became healthy.
Second, the insurance that you know that
even if there is a crisis, a pandemic, a
financial crisis, like that, the
economy falls, your money is safe, it's not,
at least it's not, it has no chance
of being lost.  good news I have
insurance that has been researched that fits into
what I said and this is it set for heal
critical illness insurance of fwd it is
called zero waz health cover Meaning
no waste no waste so
let's check its benefits this is what
I am talking about 100% refund of paid premiums
if you never made a major critical
illness claim by the h7 25 meaning everything
you paid here will be returned to you all
because you became healthy that is a reward because
you were not
able to save and save and
the beauty here is claim up
to three times meaning multiple
claims that even if you get sick
again you can claim let's say you
claimed the first time you got
money meaning then you still have
insurance so when you get sick let
's say 5 years later when you got sick
your first claim your second claim
you will have additional
claims up to 3 three times that is even if
you get sick the third time
you can claim repeatedly
there is also Ong 20% ​​coverage for minor
critical illness even if it is only minor
you can claim something You don't have to
wait for it to get worse to make a claim and  You
can catch the disease early and you won't have to
pay for it for the rest of your life. You can choose
5 years, 10 years or 20 years as
the payment period you choose.
And this is even cruel. It has a
premium waiver, meaning when you have
your first claim, you get sick,
you still have insurance. You don't
have to pay your insurance anymore. The
insurance company will pay for
it. For example, you chose 10 years to pay. So
let's say you get sick,
you claim in the second year,
you pay for the remaining 8 years of the
contract. You don't have to pay anymore,
and this is the last 100% debt benefit for
your loved ones. That means it's not just
health insurance. You also have life
insurance because. What if you die, you get
sick, you don't survive,
the beneficiary or the
person left behind will get money, and that's why you have zero recourse.
Think about it. What if you die from ACC, it's
not because of the disease.
So because you have life insurance, your
family will get something even if the
disease wasn't the cause of
the insured's death? Maybe what
you're thinking now is that it seems too good to be
true.  Won't the
insurance company lose money because of this? I wonder if
this was approved by the government or the
insurance commission. The insurance company will also make money
here by using the
premium they got from
their investment ventures, so meaning the insurance
company will release it, not you.
You, what you paid is
stated in the contract. We will be
total. There will be a financial
crisis, even if the economy collapses.
Brothers and sisters.
Link in my bio. You will be taken to
my Facebook page. Seriously, it's just
pinned. When you click on it,
you will be taken to my website. Then
click on Ong fwd insurance. Answer
my Google form and then I
will call you to assist you with
your application here.